당신이 이미 CNN에서 어떻게
파라메터를 공유하는지 알고 있습니다.
You've already seen how convolutional
network uses shared parameters across
하나의 이미지에서 patterns을 추출한 space에서..
space to extract patterns over an image.
지금은 space대신에 time이지만
같은 것을 수행할 것입니다.
Now you're going to do the same thing
but over time instead of space.
이것은 RNN 의 기반이 되는
아이디어입니다.
This is the idea behind
recurrent neural networks.
당신은 어떤 시점에서 사건의 sequence을
가지고 있다고 상상해보세요.
Imagine that you have a sequence
of events, at each point in time
그 sequence에서 일어난 일에 대해서
무언가를 결정을 내려야 합니다.
you want to make a decision about what's
happened so far in this sequence.
어떤 시점에서의 사건 event을 가지고 있고
Imagine that you have a sequence
of events, at each point in time
그 sequence에서 무언가를 결정을 해야 합니다.
you want to make a decision about
what's happened so far in the sequence.
만약 당신의 가지고 있는 sequence가
합리적으로 고정되어 있다면,
If your sequence is
reasonably stationary,
당신은 같은 시점에서 같은 분류를
사용할 수 있습니다.
you can use the same classifier
at each point in time.
그것은 이미 많은 것을 단순화합니다.
That simplifies things a lot already.
그것을 sequence이고, 지난 이력을
고려하기를 원하고 있습니다.
But since this is a sequence, you also
want to take into account the past.
어느 시점이전에는 무슨일이 있었습니다.
Everything that happened
before that point.
여기서 한 가지 자연스러운 것은
이전 분류기의 상태를 사용하는 것입니다.
One natural thing to do here is to use
the state of the previous classifier
재귀적으로 이전에 무슨 일이
발생한는지에 대한 요약과 같이..
as a summary of what happened before,
recursively.
지금은 지난 이력을 기억할 매우 깊은
neural network가 필요합니다.
Now, you would need a very deep neural
network to remember far in the past.
그 sequence는 수백, 수천의 단계라고
상상할 수 있습니다.
Imagine that this sequence could
have hundreds, thousands of steps.
이것은 수백, 수천의 layer을 갖는
deep network을 의미합니다.
It would basically mean to have
a deep network with hundreds or
thousands of layers.
그러나, 그 대신에
우리는 다시 다른 시도를 할 것이고,
But instead,
we're going to use tying again and
지난 이력을 요약할 책임이 있는
단순한 모델을 가지도록 합니다.
have a single model responsible for
summarizing the past and
당신의 분류기에 대한 정보도 제공합니다.
providing that information
to your classifier.
끝에서 얻는 것은 비교적 단순하고 반복적인
패턴을 가지고 있는 network입니다.
What you end up with is a network with a
relatively simple repeating pattern with
그 네트워크는 각각의 시점에서 입력값과
연결된 분류기의 부분들이며
part of your classifier connecting to
the input at each time step and another
recurrent connection라고 불러지는
다른 부분들과 각각의 step에서 연결되어집니다.
part called the recurrent connection
connecting you to the past at each step.